<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Distinctive Eight</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_menu">Distinctive Eight</string>

    <string name="Card_One_Description">Name a card (other than a card that has a value of 1) and choose another player. If that player has that card, he or she is out of the round.</string>
    <string name="Card_Two_Description">Look at another players hand.</string>
    <string name="Card_Three_Description">You and another player secretly compare hands. The player with the lowest value is out of the round.</string>
    <string name="Card_Four_Description">Until your next turn, ignore all effects from other players cards.</string>
    <string name="Card_Five_Description">Choose any player (including yourself) to discard his or her hand and draw a new card.</string>
    <string name="Card_Six_Description">Trade hands with another player of your choice.</string>
    <string name="Card_Seven_Description">If you have this card and either the cards with values of 6 or 5, you must discard this card.</string>
    <string name="Card_Eight_Description">If you discard this card, you are out of the round.</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_name">name</string>
    <string name="name_of_string">this is a string</string>

    <string name="how_to_play">The goal of this game is to win a total of seven rounds before the other player.
        Rounds are won by getting rid of the other players by using the affects of the cards to get them out or by
        surviving until the end of the round, when the deck runs out of cards, and being the player with the card of the largest value.

        \n\nEach round begins with shuffling the deck and the first card is put out of play. The first card is known as the Out Card and is always
        out of play and upside-down so no player can know its contents. This card stays out unless drawn by an affect of another card.

        \n\nThe game contains 16 cards with 8 different types of cards:
        \nCard 1: Name a card (other than a card that has a value of 1) and choose another player. If that player has that card, he or she is out of the round.
        \nCard 2: Look at another players hand.
        \nCard 3: You and another player secretly compare hands. The player with the lowest value is out of the round.
        \nCard 4: Until your next turn, ignore all effects from other players cards.
        \nCard 5: Choose any player (including yourself) to discard his or her hand and draw a new card from the deck. If there is no cards left in the deck, the Out Card is drawn instead.
        \nCard 6: Trade hands with another player of your choice.
        \nCard 7: If you have this card and either the cards with values of 6 or 5, you must discard this card. Once can still discard this card even if they don\'t have cards 6 or 5.
        \nCard 8: If you discard this card, you are out of the round.

    </string>

    <string name="title_activity_option">Option</string>
</resources>
